Guide to the Mount Vernon Seminary and College Mount Vernon Seminary and College graphics, publications, and administrative material collection, 1890-2000 MVC0035.MS
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs, 1875-2002; 1880-1999; Series 2
  - Events, 1940-2000; 1980-1999; Series 2 Subseries 4
    - Reunions 1998, Fall 1998; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Student Awards, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Symposium/Dinner at National Press Club, 1998 September 29; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Legacy Weekend, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Mount Vernon Tennis Classic 1999, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta event, 1999 March; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Women's Center Opening (contact sheets), 1999 March; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Spring Formal 1999, 1999 April 9; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - IN Series Dinner, 1999 May; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Family Weekend, Fall 1999; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Pancake breakfast, Fall 1999; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Blair party (alumni event), 2000 February; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Mount Vernon Tennis Classic 2000, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Elizabeth Eddy Somers - Window Dedication, Undated, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Events Undated, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Marjorie Merriweather Post, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Faculty, 1875-2000; 1880-1937; Series 2 Subseries 5
    Organized chronologically.
    The materials in Box 27 were added to this collection later. These materials have been separately arranged in chronological order.
    - Easton, Miss S. A., Circa 1875; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chickering, Frances Elizabeth (biographical information), 1875-1877; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - "Grandma Eddy", Circa late 1800s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Smith, Dr. Julie E. ("The Little Doctor"), Circa 1880; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Group photos - women in dinner dresses, Circa 1880s; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Miss Theodate Louise, 1886-1898; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Porte, Miss Caroline, 1887 June; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Woodhull, Miss Marianne, 1890-1892; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Faculty member (initials G.L.T.), Circa 1892-1902; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Nash, Frances (American pianist), 1907-1908; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Faculty/staff at 1100 M Street, NW, 1908-1909; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Curtis, Helen (Mrs. Luther R. Fowle) - teacher 1908-1910, Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Peltier, Mme. Eleanore, 1910-1937; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Faculty 1925-1926, Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Eaton, Miss Isabel, 1937 May 16; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Faculty 1950-1959, Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Faculty 1980-1989, Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Pearson, Carol (Dean - Mount Vernon Institute), Spring 1995; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Carroll, Senorita Maria (faculty emeritus), Fall 2000; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Undated, Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Miss Guard leading school from chapel during commencement, undated; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Students, 1875-1999; 1880-1950; Series 2 Subseries 6
    The materials in Boxes 27 and 28 were added to this collection later. These materials have been separately arranged in chronological order.
    - Bliss, Clara B., 1875-1876; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Hart, Isabel, Circa late 1800s; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Hoard, Bessie, Circa late 1800s; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Burr, Addie Perry, 1875-1888; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Golden Jubilee Calendar (features images of Mrs. Minnie Naylor Swartzell and Mrs. Mary Stewart Carey), 1875-1925; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Hawley, Ida Margaret, 1876-1879; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Andrus, Ida Munson - Class of 1878, 1877-1878; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Eddy, Florence (Mrs. Edwin A. Root), 1877-1879; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Chase, Fannie Robinson [Class of 1881], 1877-1881; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Cordell, Sallie I., 1878-1879; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Bates, Nellie Groome, 1878-1881; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Hogue, Alma Marie [Class of 1881], 1878-1881; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Koehne, Anna Bagge, 1878-1941; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Goodwin, Myra [Class of 1880], 1879-1880; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Barnes, Mary Alice, 1879-1881; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Leech, Elizabeth Beall [Class of 1882], 1879-1882; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Hall, Edith Alden, Circa 1880s; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Andrews, Grace - Class of 1885, 1880-1885; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Calder, Regina [Class of 1882], 1880-1882; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Killinger, Flora C., 1880-1882; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Heilman, Rose, 1880-1884; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Hill, Alice Lanier, 1880-1884; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Coffin, Rachel Jones [Class of 1888], 1880-1888; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Carroll, Minnie, 1881-1883; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Jennings, Mary "Mimi" [Class of 1883], 1881-1883; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Foster, Eleanor (Mrs. Robert Lansing) [Class of 1884], 1881-1934; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Blount, Mary, 1882-1883; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Gallup, Abbie Rosaline, 1882-1883; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Barry, Margaret G., 1883-1884; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Battles, C. Elizabeth, 1883-1884; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Cannon, Mabel Frances [Class of 1886], 1883-1886; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Filbert, Corinne Reitzell, 1883-1886; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Edwards, Alice Elsie, 1883-1893; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Lacey, Edith, 1884; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Anderson, Clara Harrison, 1884-1885; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Farwell, Cornelia "Nellie" Hannah, 1884-1885; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Foster, Lila, 1884-1885; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - "The Wicked Five", Circa 1884-1885; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Baldwin, Maria, 1884-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Brouse, H. Grace, 1884-1888; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Lemon, Martha "Mattie" Louise [Class of 1888], 1884-1888; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Kuki, Yoshiko, 1884-1890; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Brush, Nellie [Class of 1891], 1884-1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Kuki, Yoshiko (supporting materials), 1884-1999; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Torinars, Grace, 1885; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Barton, Lillian Avis, 1885-1886; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Bowman, Genevieve Elizabeth, 1885-1886; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Flagg, Minnie, 1885-1886; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Groups - Nell Brush, Vernie Weaver and Ida Weaver, 1885-1886; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Haydock, Mellie [Class of 1886], 1885-1886; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Bell, May (pictured with Bunnie Bullene), 1885-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Bullene, Lora A. "Bonnie/Bunny", 1885-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Carskaddon, Erba Mond, 1885-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Cheney, Agnes, 1885-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - DeLaittre, Corinne, 1885-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Eighmey, Augusta [Class of 1887], 1885-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Groups - includes Mary Norton, Sally Wartman, Laura Dawson, Circa 1885-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Luce, Alethea H. [Class of 1887], 1885-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Dill, Anna, 1885-1888; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - DePauw, Florence Leyden [Class of 1889], 1885-1889; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Keen, Eugenia "Jeanne" [Class of 1889], 1885-1889; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Daily, Jessie, 1886-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Daily, Mary Shirley, 1886-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Dobbins, Mae L., 1886-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Griswold, Mabel, 1886-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Group - Mellie Haydock and May Clarke, 1886-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Groups - five students, 1886-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Hayward, Jean, 1886-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Krag, Florence, 1886-1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Huston, Sallie Clay, 1886-1889; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Clarke, Marianne "May", 1886-1937; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Davis, Anna M., 1887; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Groups - Bunnie Bullene, Florence DePauw, Augusta Eighmey, Frances Sooville, Carrie Porte, Lina Wilson, Cora Warner, H. Grace Brouse, 1887 June; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Birdsall, Adelaide, 1887-1888; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Bradford, Mary Knight (Mrs. George Winchester Stone) - Class of 1888, 1887-1888; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Heffelfinger, Nell, 1887-1888; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Ford, Connie Webb, 1887-1889; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Guard, Jessie Lorna, 1887-1889; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Dingley, Edith [Class of 1890], 1887-1890; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Firestone, May, 1887-1890; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Dill, Alice Haywood, 1887-1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Gamble, Helen Burt, 1887-1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Clapp, Alice J., 1887-1893; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Herrick, Elizabeth "Izzie" Anne [Class of 1891], 1887-1905; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Baird, Blanche M., 1888-1889; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Clapp, Lydia S., 1888-1889; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Hill, Joan, 1888-1889; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - DeRossett, Annie, 1888-1890; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Baird, Myrtle - Class of 1892, 1888-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Farrar, Zoe [Class of 1892], 1888-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Hurst, Helen [Class of 1892], 1888-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Mazie Florence Killingsworth [Class of 1894], 1888-1894; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Cook, Edith Denison [Class of 1890], 1889-1890; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Gallup, Clara Louise, 1889-1890; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Beebe, Anna Coryell - Class of 1891, 1889-1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Calder, Phila Lazarus [Class of 1891], 1889-1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Chamberlin, Elsa Durand [Class of 1891], 1889-1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Dean, Grace Fleetwood, 1889-1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Field, Elizabeth "Lizzie" Hardin [Class of 1891], 1889-1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Groups - Georgie Conway and Grace Dean, 1889-1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Carr, Lida Morehead, 1889-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Choate, Katherine Miriam [Class of 1892], 1889-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Eddy, Elizabeth, 1889-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Hasselman, Anna [Class of 1892] - Teacher at MVS (1908-1915), 1889-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Lake, Lilian Abbott [Class of 1899], 1889-1899; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Dufour, Dora Elise [Class of 1894] - MVS Faculty (1898, 1910-1914), 1889-1914; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Clubs - V.V. (Charter Members), Circa 1890; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Emery, Julia, 1890-1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Booge, Laura Elizabeth - Class of 1892, 1890-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Brown, Catharine F. [Class of 1892], 1890-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Hammond, Bertha Elizabeth [Class of 1892], 1890-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Groups - Hallowe'en Babies, Circa 1890-1893; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Groups - Mary Woodson, Ina Taft, Caryl Hendricks, Eugenis Keen, Circa 1890s; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Groups - Walking-mates (includes Anna Hasselman, Anna Sargent, and Bertha Nesbit), 1890s; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Cox, Margaret [Class of 1900], 1890-1900; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Ford, Nellie Blanche (Mrs. Harry Norton Torrey) [Class of 1892], 1890-1930; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Group - The Triangle (Clara Seipp, Ephie Crawford, and Helen Gamble), 1891; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Doyle, Grace Alice [Class of 1892], 1891-1892; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Horton, Belle Rogers, 1891-1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Birney, Edith - Class of 1897, 1891-1897; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Hubbell, Beulah Cooper (Countess Wachtmeister) [Class of 1893], 1891-1899; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Barnitz, Blanche Clare - Class of 1893, 1892-1893; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Brand, Hedwig - Class of 1894, 1892-1894; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Humphrey, Ethel Rose, 1892-1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Bell, Elsie May (daughter of Alexander Graham Bell), 1892-1897; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Edwards, Elsie, 1893; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Groups - Candids from 1100 M Street campus, 1893-1894; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Groups - Four photos including one in Adele Corning's room, 1893-1894; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Groups - 'The Record' editors (Elsie Edwards and Hedwig Brand), 1893-1894; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Gunnison, Ritchie, 1893-1894; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Bryant, Carolyn Bell (also pictured Mary McCoy), 1893-1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Coleman, Louise Lord, 1893-1896; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Butler, Jenna May [Class of 1899], 1893-1899; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Janney, Grace McPherson [Class of 1900], 1893-1900; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Gardner, Helen B. and Elise C., 1893-1904; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Group - Nell Hosea and Jennie Woodson (roommates), 1894; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Hancock, Edith Stark [Class of 1894], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Wright, Grace, 1894; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Bailey, Bessie Carlton, 1894-1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Barrett, Florence E., 1894-1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Eddy, Mary Olive, 1894-1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Gould, Elsie, 1894-1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Hosea, Leonora, 1894-1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Loomis, Edna, 1894-1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Brown, Eleanor N., 1894-1896; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Cameron, Flora McDonald, 1894-1896; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Clark, Flora Louise, 1894-1896; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Cleveland, Edith G., 1894-1896; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Gale, Olive (Mrs. William C. Hill), 1894-1906; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Baber, Blanche - Class of 1895, Circa 1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Gros, Honora Patton (biographical information), 1895; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Hollweg, Julia, 1895-1896; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Leas, Mabel A., 1895-1896; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Hastings, Florence, 1895-1897; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - Heefner, Bernice Thomas [Class of 1897], 1895-1897; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - Ford, Stella Dunbar [Class of 1898], 1895-1898; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Group - Grace Janney, Alice Dewey, and Florence Hall, 1895-1898; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - Dewey, Katharine, 1895-1899; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - Groups - Helen Walter and Sadie Britton, 1895-1901; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Edmonston, Leila (Mrs. Benjamin DeWitt Riegel), 1895-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - Janney, Caroline W. [Class of 1896], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - Knapp, Mollie [Class of 1896], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - Sowers, Eleanor (Mrs. Samson Lane Faison) [Class of 1896] - newspaper clippings, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 64)
    - Group - Mollie Knapp and Grace Phillips, 1896-1897; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 65)
    - Jackson, Mary Woodin [Class of 1897], 1896-1897; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 66)
    - Adams, Alice Montgomerie - Class of 1898, 1897-1898; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Birch, Helen Louise, 1897-1898; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Deterding, Maude Evelyn [Class of 1898], 1897-1898; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 67)
    - Artman, Pauline - Class of 1899, 1897-1899; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Carey, Martha, 1897-1899; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 68)
    - Groups - Katherine Dewey and Marion Dall, 1897-1899; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 69)
    - Eddy, Lucy, 1897-1900; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 70)
    - Group - Bliss Finley, Marion Dall, Ralph Johnson, Alfred Hamson, and Joe Hamson, 1897-1900; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - Groups - Includes Grace Janney, Catherine Ridgely, Marion Dall, Ruth Halford, and Helen Hill, 1897-1901; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Dimmick, Jessie Lawrence [Class of 1900], 1897-1910; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 72)
    - Bell, Grace (Mrs. Granville Fortescue), 1897-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 73)
    - Class of 1898, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Bond, Elfleda E., 1898-1899; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Breneman, Helen - Class of 1901, 1898-1901; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Fry, Edith Gillis (Mrs. William E. Pearson) [Class of 1907], 1898-1930; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 74)
    - Fletcher, Elizabeth [Class of 1899], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 75)
    - Ker, Roberta, 1899-1901; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 76)
    - Ingram, Florence Teresa [Class of 1902], 1899-1902; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 35, Folder 77)
    - Ingram, Mary Dosh [Class of 1903], 1899-1903; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Edmonston, Frances Mildred [Class of 1907], 1899-1907; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Groups - Includes Gertrude Hinman, Mae Press, Lucy Tolerton, and Jana Black, 1900; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Bartlett, Eleanor - Class of 1902, 1900-1902; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Lauck, Lucy Donaldson [Class of 1909], 1900-1909; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Reproductions of early photos ca. late 19th early 20th century, Circa 1900-1930; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Eleanor Lansing Dulles photocopies of family photographs, 1900-1954; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Clubs - V.V., Circa 1901; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Eddy, Josephine Morris, 1901; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Beckwith, Gertrude Jerome (Mrs. Charles Lee McIlvaine) - biographical information, 1901-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1902, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Stotzenburg, Jane (Mrs. Leon B. Kromer), 1902-1906; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Student Organizations - V.V., 1902-1909; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Barry, Elizabeth (Mrs. Sevellon Brown), 1902-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Bush, Bertha Vernell (Mrs. Victor I. Minahan) [Class of 1904], 1902-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - B.T.S. Society, 1903-1904; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Gardner, Margaret (Mrs. George D. Hulet), 1903-1907; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Groups, 1903-1908; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Day, Mary (Mrs. Oliver T. Boyd) [Class of 1904], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Lacy, Carolyn, 1904; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Boone, Belle - Class of 1905, Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Groups, Circa 1905; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Hill, Helen (Mrs. George M. Hawes), 1905-1906; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Berger, Helen, 1906-1907; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Baum, Brownie Elisabeth (Brownie Bess) - Class of 1908, 1906-1908; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Bready, Agnes Ballock - Class of 1907 (newspaper clipping), 1907-1936; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - French, Ruth, 1908-1909; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Groups - Candid photographs, 1908-1909; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - M Street students, 1908-1909; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Picnic at country home of Harriet Lothrop, 1908-1909; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Anderson, Ruth (Mrs. Harold S. Wheeler/ Mrs. Louis McLaughlin Blankenhorn), 1908-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Cook, Louise [Class of 1909], Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Cleveland, Theo Frances [Class of 1913], 1909-1913; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Gorton, Gretchen, 1910-1912; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Hawk, Lucy W. (Mrs. Wendell Lovell Smith) [Class of 1912], 1910-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Anderson, Marion Jeanette - Class of 1913, 1911-1913; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Austin, Emma Yawkey - Class of 1914 (biographical information), 1911-1935; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Alexander, Marjorie, 1912; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 28, Folder 17)